http://www.mybabyshowerfavors.com/privacypolicy.html

Questions?
Contact Us at 321-200-0694 orClick-to-call: 321-200-0694Click-to-call
Contact Us
View CartTop PicksPopularUnique Baby Shower FavorsUnder $2.00PersonalizedCookiesCandlesEdible FavorsCandyMintsChocolateBrowniesCoffee, Tea and Drink FavorsCategoriesMirror Compact FavorsMake Your OwnBath, Body, and SoapBaby Picture FramesCrystal FavorsSeed PacketsPurse HoldersPopular ItemsMagnetsKeychainsBookmarksCookie Cutter FavorsPersonalized TagsTowel FavorsBottle StoppersPen & Notebook FavorsSuppliesSuppliesDecorationsTablewareCenterpiecesGamesGiftsBaby Shower GiftsCostCheap Baby Shower Favors (Under $1)Inexpensive ($1-$2)Other OccasionsChristening & BaptismFather's DayJuly 4thOther LinksFAQTestimonialsBaby Shower IdeasBaby Gender CalculatorMenu
Home
About Us
Order Info
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
View Cart
Top PicksPopularUnique Baby Shower FavorsUnder $2.00PersonalizedCookiesCandlesEdible FavorsCandyMintsChocolateBrowniesCoffee, Tea and Drink FavorsCategoriesMirror Compact FavorsMake Your OwnBath, Body, and SoapBaby Picture FramesCrystal FavorsSeed PacketsPurse HoldersPopular ItemsMagnetsKeychainsBookmarksCookie Cutter FavorsPersonalized TagsTowel FavorsBottle StoppersPen & Notebook FavorsSuppliesSuppliesDecorationsTablewareCenterpiecesGamesGiftsBaby Shower GiftsCostCheap Baby Shower Favors (Under $1)Inexpensive ($1-$2)Other OccasionsChristening & BaptismFather's DayJuly 4thOther LinksFAQTestimonialsBaby Shower IdeasBaby Gender Calculator
Pinterest
This
site is hosted by Yahoo's Aabaco Small Business. Aabaco hosts the store pages, ordering
system, and order data. Aabaco automatically collects order information
but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this
store through Yahoo! Shopping, Aabaco also automatically collects information
about your shopping experience. Please see the Yahoo's Privacy Policy for
more information about how Yahoo uses this information.
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
Our Commitment To Privacy
The Information We Collect
How We Use Information
Our Commitment To Data Security
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
How To Access Or Correct Your Information
How To Contact Us
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide
this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices
you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To
make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage
and at every point where personally identifiable information may be
requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted
on the My Baby Shower Favors website. On some pages, you can order products,
make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal
information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
(etc.)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example,
if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient,
you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance,
the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
(etc.)
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when
placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information
with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that
order.
We use the information you provide about someone else
when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery.
We do not share this information with outside parties except to the
extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer personalized items by which you can personalize
a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us
to create an item is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed
to the person receiving the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we
receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not
shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like
to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services.
Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose
unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to
better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example,
we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain
area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled
out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could
be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable
information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described
above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise
prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy,
and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate
physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially
important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information
at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part
of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information
that we collect online and maintain by emailing us. We use this procedure
to better safeguard your information. You can
correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by
sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take
reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making
corrections.
Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, click here.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these
privacy policies, please send us an email
at
.
Decorated Cookies | Articles | Our Blog
Copyright © 2004-2020 - My Baby Shower Favors
